(Penny:)Maybe she'd be more comfortable
meeting a girl first.
- Good idea. Bernadette?
- What the hell?
(Raj:)Well, you're very pretty, that could
be intimidating to another woman.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah.
(Bernadette:)Hey, you don't think I'm pretty enough
to scare your girlfriend?
(Howard:)Calm down, Bernie, you're very scary.
(Amy:)It should be me.
(Raj:)Why? So you can make jokes
about cutting open my brain?
A, that was not ajoke,
that was a sincere request.
(Amy:)And B, more importantly,
I was the outsider to this group...
(Amy:)...and I know how frightening that can be.
(Amy:)But you guys took me in
and made me feel loved, like I was family.
(Sheldon:)Fine, I'll do it.
(Amy:)So after I started dating Sheldon,
I met Leonard and then everybody else...
(Amy:)...and they've all been so wonderful to me.
(Lucy:)That's really nice to hear.